KEDARNATH PANDYA

+44 7570309219 kedarnathpandya@gmail.com

75, Shakespeare Drive Harrow, HA3 9TR London, United Kingdom





PROFILE

iOS Developer with 3 months of industrial experience. I am developing mobile applications in this operating system and iPadOS since 2018. Have a good amount of knowledge in Swift Programming and Swift-UI. Developed more than 25 mobile applications. Also developed mobile applications with some advanced technology such as Machine Learning and AR (Augmented reality). Set a bunch of applications in AR while learning the concepts of AR.

EXPERIENCE

iOS Developer Intern, Coronation Solutions PVT LTD, Ahmedabad, India — September-2020 - December 2020

I completed 3 month Internship as an iOS developer in Coronation Solutions Private Limited. During the internship learned core fundamental of Swift programming language. Developed an E-Commerce mobile application during the internship.

Crew Member, McDonald's, London, UK — September-2022 - Present

I am serving as a crew member in McDonald's, Neasden branch.
McDonald's assigned me Cash (Till) Counter and customer representative.
In this role, I have been dealing with many customers to take their orders, provide them services and solve their issues. During this job, I gain knowledge about customer dealing and advisory.

PROJECTS

Blood Spot — Graduation Year Project

Blood spot is an online blood / plasma donation website that was developed by me and my teammates as our final year graduation project.

I guided my team as a leader and decided the content of the project. I managed all the paperwork such as presentation and reports.

Mobile Application Development — Personalise Project

Developed iOS applications that are based on swift and swift UI programming languages. While I was learning iOS 11 and iOS 13 I developed these mobile application.

Augmented Reality & 3-D Object Animation — Personalised Project

Developed mobile application in iOS platform with advance technology such as Machine Learning and Augmented Reality. Also create 3-D object with the help of Apple's pre written photogrammetry command line application.

Web Development — Personalised Project

Developed my own iOS developer portfolio for learning purpose.

SKILLS

- iOS/ iPadOS/ Mobile Application Developer
- Augmented Reality Mobile Application Developer
- Machine Learning Mobile Application Developer
- 3-D Object Animator
- Familiar with Swift and Swift-UI programming languages
- Website Developer
- · Video Editor (iMovies)

EDUCATION

University Of Greenwich, London, United Kingdom — September 2022-Ongoing Swarnim Startup and Innovation University, Gandhinagar, India — 2017-2021

CERTIFICATE

- Startup Project Swarnim Startup and Innovation University August 2021
- Apple Teacher & Apple Swift Playground Teacher Apple August 2020
- iOS 13 & Swift 5 Development Bootcamp Udemy June 2020
- Data Science and Machine Learning Using Python ADHOC Network -February 2020
- iOS 11 Developer Course Udemy January 2020